A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Religious Interests, Series N FA323
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - National Preaching Mission, 1936-1940 (Box 32, Folder 252)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd's contribution, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s great interest in the activities of the Mission, his contributions, brochure of letters of efforts. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, James M. Speers, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Charles Evans Hughes.
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - Work in Canal Zone, 1922-1948 (Box 32, Folder 253)
    Pleas for contributions to churches in Canal Zone, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s pledge to Union Church in the Canal Zone, Building Fund, church activities. Correspondents include Roy B. Guild, Arthur W. Packard.
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - International Justice and Goodwill, 1921-1934, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 254)
    Work of commission, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s pledges. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard, Raymond B. Fosdick.
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - Interchange Commission for the Exchange of Preachers, 1919-1927 (Box 32, Folder 255)
    Interchange of British and American ministers, cancellation of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s program of speaking to American soldiers in France. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s donation to Commission, minutes of meetings. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Rev. Dugald Macfadyen, H. Fosdick, Willard S. Richardson.
    73.1
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1924-1959 (Box 32, Folder 256)
    Work of Conference, appeals denied, reconsideration, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s congratulations to Henry Ford on repudiation of anti-semitism. Plans for Brotherhood Week programs, reports of activities. Correspondents include Arthur W. Packard, Robert W. Straus, Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Alfred Williams Anthony, Willard S. Richardson, Nelson A. Rockefeller.
    73.2
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - National Conference of Christians and Jews - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Contributions, 1939-1959 (Box 33, Folder 257)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contributions to budget, renewal of pledges, contributions to Williams College Institute of Human Relations, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller's contributions. Correspondents include Everett Clinchy, Arthur W. Packard.
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - National Conference of Christians and Jews - David Rockefeller, 1946-1961 (Box 33, Folder 258)
    Requests that David Rockefeller contribute to or participate in work of conference, all declined. Correspondents include David Rockefeller, Arthur W. Packard, Dana S. Creel.
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - National Conference of Christians and Jews - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1933-1961 (Box 33, Folder 259)
    John D. Rockefeller 3rd personal contributions until 1950, then through Rockefeller Brothers Foundation. Declinations of personal participation in events. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Arthur W. Packard.
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - National Conference of Christians and Jews - Laurance S. Rockefeller, 1952-1961 (Box 33, Folder 260)
    Appeals declined. Laurance S. Rockefeller gave address, June 12, 1961 honoring Michael Daroff. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, Dana S. Creel.
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - Council on World Tensions, Inc.
    Formerly World Organization for Brotherhood. Activities. Proposed mission to Asia. John D. Rockefeller 3rd made two contributions. Correspondents include Laurance S. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller 3rd.
    73.3
    - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - Council on World Tensions, Inc., 1950-1958 (Box 33, Folder 261)
    - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - Council on World Tensions, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 33, Folder 262)
    - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America - Council on World Tensions, Inc., 1959-1961 (Box 33, Folder 262A)
- Fifth Avenue Baptist Church
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - General, 1898-1917 (Box 33, Folder 263)
    Building plans, John D. Rockefeller's resignation as trustee, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution for new church, subscription lists, financial assistance for student, church membership discussion, list of correspondence destroyed. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Rev. R. P. Johnson, Frederick T. Gates, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., William H. Hays, Addison Moore, Cornelius Woelfkin, Willard S. Richardson.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - Dr. Aked Correspondence, 1906-1907 (Box 34, Folder 264)
    Acceptance of call as minister, Dr. Aked's illness, church affairs, Willard S. Richardson appointment as Associate Pastor, publication of sermons, Italian mission work in New York City, gift of books to poor ministers, resignation, plans for new building. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s gifts. Church relations. Correspondents include Edgar S. Marston, Charles F. Aked, W. H. P. Faunce, Starr J. Murphy, Charles Evans Hughes, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., E. L. Ballard, Charles O. Heydt.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - Dr. Aked Correspondence, 1908-April 1910 (Box 34, Folder 265)
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - Dr. Aked Correspondence, June 1910-1924 (Box 34, Folder 266)
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - New Building, 1916-1925 (Box 34, Folder 267)
    Decision to sell property, possible merger with Calvary Church, family decision to contribute half of funds needed for new church. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., W. M. Crane, W. R. Conklin, Charles Evans Hughes, E. L. Ballard.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - New Building - Architects Plans and Fees, 1917-1922 (Box 34, Folder 268)
    Selection of Pelton as architect, Allen & Collens as consulting architects, builders' estimates, architects' fees. Correspondents include E. L. Ballard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., H. C. Pelton, Charles Collens.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - New Building - Communion Table, 1924-1926, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 269)
    Gift of twelve wooden figures to be used in construction of communion table. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., E. L. Ballard, W. R. Conklin, H. C. Pelton, Messrs. Heimat-Kunst.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - New Building - Marc Eidlitz and Company, 1920-1922 (Box 34, Folder 270)
    Agreement to erect building at cost plus 7 1/2%. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Robert Eidlitz.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - Investments, 1903, 1908-1922 (Box 34, Folder 271)
    Trustees' approval of recommendation to invest trust funds, status of each fund, list of securities held by church, purchases of stock. Investments made from Rockefeller Trust Fund. List of purchases. Correspondents include W. S. Lovett, Colgate Hoyt, E. L. Marston, W. M. Crane, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Bertram Cutler.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - New Building - Organ, 1919-1928 (Box 35, Folder 272)
    Contract with Hook & Hastings Company to construct new organ, specifications, installation and payment, alterations to chamber. Correspondents include E. L. Ballard, H. C. Pelton, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Archer Gibson, H. V. Milligan.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - New Building - Organ - J. B. Trevor and Miss Trevor, 1920-1928 (Box 35, Folder 273)
    Gift of organ from J. B. Trevor and Emily Trevor as memorial to their father, installation costs. Correspondents include J. B. Trevor, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., W. R. Conklin, Miss Emily Trevor, E. L. Ballard.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - New Building - Organ - Re Organ and Committee on Memorials, 1921-1929 (Box 35, Folder 274)
    Appointment of Committee, resolutions adopted on memorial windows, types of memorials preferred and location of bronze tablets, recommendations on stained-glass makers, installation of Mason Memorial Window. Correspondents include W. R. Conklin, Robert W. Gumbel, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., E. L. Ballard, C. Woelfkin, W. Bosworth, A. Trevor, E. C. Carder.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - New Building - Prospectus and Plans for New Church, 1910 (Box 35, Folder 275)
    Printed volume containing prospectus and plans for proposed church with a brief history, 1910.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - New Building - Rockefeller Pledges, 1917-1926 (Box 35, Folder 276)
    Contributions from John D. Rockefeller and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. toward Building Fund of church, matching contributions made by congregation, gift to church from Rockefeller Foundation. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., E. L. Ballard, Herbert W. Todd, Charles O. Heydt, William M. Crane.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - New Building - Gifts from John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Children, 1920-1922 (Box 35, Folder 277)
    Pledges by the children to the Church Building Fund, receipts for payment. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, Willard S. Richardson, Robert W. Gumbel, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Winthrop Rockefeller, Abby Rockefeller Mauzé.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - Systematic Benevolences, 1916-1922 (Box 35, Folder 278)
    John D. Rockefeller and Laura Spelman Rockefeller pledge, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. pledge. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Herbert Hill, Willard S. Richardson.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - Property - Offers for Property, 1925-1929 (Box 35, Folder 279)
    Possible acquisition by Madison Avenue Baptist Church, sale to Central Presbyterian Church, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s assumption of mortgage. Correspondents include W. R. Conklin, Philip Keebler, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., E. L. Ballard.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - Property - Purchase of 64th Street Property, 1917-1920 (Box 35, Folder 280)
    Purchase of property southeast corner 64th Street and Park Avenue by John D. Rockefeller, Jr., deeding it to Church. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., W. R. Conklin, E. L. Ballard.
  - Fifth Avenue Baptist Church - Property - Sale of 46th Street Property, 1919-1923 (Box 35, Folder 281)
    Appointment of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. as Chairman of Finance Committee, purchase of property by Dreicer & Company. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., William A. White & Sons, Charles O. Heydt.
- Park Avenue Baptist Church
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Miscellaneous; Associate Membership; 1926 Action, 1923-1926 (Box 35, Folder 282)
    Revision of conditions of church membership, copy of resolutions adopted eliminating members enrolled as associate members. Correspondents include E. L. Ballard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., C. Woelfkin.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Rev. Eugene Carder, 1922-1930 (Box 35, Folder 283)
    Gifts and salary payments to Mr. Carder, friendly sentiments. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Eugene C. Carder.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Ministers for Church, 1924-1925 (Box 35, Folder 284)
    James G. Gilkey.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Christmas and Thanksgiving Funds for Church Employees, 1922-1928 (Box 35, Folder 285)
    Sending of checks as contribution to Church Employees' Christmas Fund and to Woman's Society Thanksgiving and Christmas Funds. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Mrs. Edward L. Ballard, Charles O. Heydt, Willard S. Richardson.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Pensions - Dr. Woelfkin and Dr. Carder, 1923-1925 (Box 35, Folder 286)
    Participation of Dr. Carder and Dr. Woelfkin in Baptist Ministers' Pension Fund. Correspondents include Stephen A. Van Ness, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., E. C. Carder, C. Woelfkin, E. L. Ballard.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - The Misses Pettus, 1926-1940 (Box 35, Folder 287)
    Financial assistance to the Pettus sisters. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., E. C. Carder, Robert W. Gumbel.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Summer Bible Class, 1923-1927 (Box 35, Folder 288)
    Conducting of Summer Bible Class at John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s expense. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., E. C. Carder.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Dr. Woelfkin's Resignation, 1925-1927 (Box 35, Folder 289)
    Letter of resignation, May 10, 1925, testimonial, reception to Dr. Woelfkin, January 12, 1926. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., C. Woelfkin, Arthur E. Bestor, Marshall Clark, J. Howard Audry.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Contributions to Building Fund, 1917-1923, 1942-1943, 1951, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 290)
    Letters to various individuals soliciting funds for building of new church, gifts from various church organizations and from estate of William Rockefeller. Pledge list. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Colgate Hoyt, W. M. Crane, Charles O. Heydt, C. Woelfkin, W. L. Ballard, William Rockefeller.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Contributions to Building Fund - E. L. Marston, 1917-1922 (Box 36, Folder 291)
    Efforts to secure additional pledge from Mr. Marston. Correspondents include Edgar L. Marston, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Church School - General, 1922-1929 (Box 36, Folder 292)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr. gifts to Church School, authorizations for purchases, contribution to United Parents Exposition. Personnel selection. Appointment of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to Church School Committee. Correspondents include E. C. Carder, Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., S. Van Ness.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Church School - Authorizations/Contributions - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1922-1929 (Box 36, Folder 293)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contributions, authorizations for purchases, United Parents Exposition. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Anna L. Moore, J. M. Pratt, Raymond B. Fosdick.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Church School - Director of Religious Education, 1927-1929 (Box 36, Folder 294)
    Proposed candidates for the position, calling of Rev. Ivar Hellstrom. Correspondents include Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Church School - S. R. Bishop, 1922-1928 (Box 36, Folder 295)
    Appointment to play piano at Church School and as Treasurer offerings. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Samuel R. Bishop, A. Moore, H. P. Fish.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Church School - Mrs. Sophie Fahs, 1923-1924 (Box 36, Folder 296)
    Appointment as Church School teacher, misbehavior of David Rockefeller in Church School. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., S. Fahs, A. Moore.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Church School - Mrs. Sophie Fahs, 1924 (Box 36, Folder 296A)
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Church School - Miss Anna L. Moore, 1922-1930 (Box 36, Folder 297)
    Acceptance of position as Director of Religious Education, re-appointment. Miss Moore's resignation as Church School Director. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Anna L. Moore.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Church School - Miss Julia D. Stevens, 1922-1923 (Box 36, Folder 298)
    Employment as Superintendent of Beginners' and Primary Department of Church School. Resignation.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Church School - Miss Alma Schilling, 1922-1932 (Box 36, Folder 299)
    Hiring as Superintendent of Junior Department, re-appointments, salary arrangements. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Miss Schilling, H. P. Fish, I. Hellstrom.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Miscellaneous, 1920-1925 (Box 36, Folder 300)
    Resignation of Mark R. MacDonnell as sexton, relieving Dr. Woelfkin of administrative details. Loan of money to student, purchase of stereoptican for new building. Baptism of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s sons. Dr. Fosdick's views on theological questions, invitation to Stephen Hammond to join church, gift to Memorial Flower Fund. Joy that Winthrop Rockefeller and David Rockefeller are joining the church, possible names for new church, Harold Phillips' declination of offer to come to Riverside. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution to Near East Relief. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., C. Woelfkin, E. C. Carder, E. L. Ballard, Willard S. Richardson, Stephen H. Hammond, H. E. Fosdick, Rev. Harold C. Phillips.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Miscellaneous, 1926-1930 (Box 36, Folder 301)
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Miscellaneous, 1927 (Box 36, Folder 301A)
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Chimes, 1921-1923 (Box 36, Folder 302)
    Letters to various firms requesting information on furnishing and installation of chimes, report on housing chimes, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s visit to Gloucester, Massachusetts, to hear carillon at Church of Our Lady of Good Voyage, abandonment of plan to install chimes for carillon, itinerary of Mayer's European trip. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., E. L. Ballard, Allen & Collens, Buchanan Houston, H. C. Pelton, C. Woelfkin, F. C. Mayer.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Carillon - Bell Inscription and Memorial Tablet, 1923-1925 (Box 36, Folder 303)
    Agreement on wording, cost of installation of tablet, dedication program. Correspondents include F. C. Mayer, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., M. Eidlitz & Son, Robert W. Gumbel.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Carillon - John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Pledge for Tower and Carillon, 1922-1927 (Box 36, Folder 304)
    Contribution of tower and carillon funds as memorial to his mother, sending of checks to Church, cost of carillon. Correspondents include W. M. Crane, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., H. C. Pelton, Marc Eidlitz & Sons, Robert W. Gumbel.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Carillon - Re Anton Brees, 1924-1928 (Box 37, Folder 305)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s request with Taylor & Company, delay in completion of carillon, test of the bells at foundry, resignation as carilloneur employment at Mercersburg Academy, recital at Park Avenue Church. Correspondents include F. C. Mayer, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Anton Brees, E. Denison Taylor, C. F. Johnston, Robert W. Gumbel, E. C. Carder.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Carillon - Brees Controversy, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 306)
    List of Mr. Brees' recitals, severance of friendly relations with Mr. Mayer, resignation as carilloneur, cancellation of contract. Correspondents include Frederick Rocke, Carder, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., F. C. Mayer, Thomas M. Debevoise.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Carillon - Contract with Gillett and Johnston, 1923-1926 (Box 37, Folder 307)
    Between Cyril F. Johnston and John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to manufacture carillon for church, assignment of interest to church, settlement of bill, shipment of bells. Correspondents include A. L. Boulware, W. R. Conklin, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Robert W. Gumbel, James M. Pratt, F. C. Mayer.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Carillon - Gillett, Johnston, Mayer Correspondence, 1923-1930 (Box 37, Folder 308)
    Award of contract for carillon, layout for installation, testing of bells, shipment. Name for carillon, gift for Trocadero Organ Restoration Fund. Correspondents include C. Woelfkin, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Ivy Lee, F. C. Mayer, W. R. Conklin, Gillett & Johnston, Arthur Woods, Thomas M. Debevoise, Charles O. Heydt.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Carillon - Kamiel Lefevre, 1925-1929 (Box 37, Folder 309)
    Recital at church, July 30, 1926, Price's resignation, summer mid-week recitals, signing of three year contract. Pledge, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. to church. Correspondents include F. C. Mayer, Kamiel Lefevre, Robert W. Gumbel, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., W. M. Crane, Hugh Bancroft, E. L. Ballard.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Carillon - F. P. Price, 1925-1927 (Box 37, Folder 310)
    Invitation to play carillon, salary arrangements, his resignation. Mr. Price contract. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s agreement to reimburse church for 1926. Correspondents include Robert W. Gumbel, F. P. Price, W. M. Crane, W. R. Conklin.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Carillon - Articles and Photographs, 1925-1926 (Box 37, Folder 311)
    Clippings and photographs re costing the bells, visit of King George V and Queen Mary to foundry, complaints from Park Avenue neighbors about carillon noise. Correspondents include Robert W. Gumbel, W. R. Conklin.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Stained Glass Windows, 1922-1925 (Box 37, Folder 312)
    Pamphlet The Flemish Stained Glass Windows, proposed designs for windows, purchase shipment and installation, photographing the windows, detailed cost of installation, distribution of the descriptive pamphlet to libraries and art museums, dedication as memorial to Mrs. Jennie Colorado Hunter Marston by her family, sending of cuts to the church. Correspondents include Roy G. Thomas, E. L. Ballard, Wilfred Drake, C. Woelfkin, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Hunter S. Marston.
  - Park Avenue Baptist Church - Systematic Benevolences, 1921-1929 (Box 37, Folder 313)
    Pledges made by members of the family, summary of church budgetary requirements, pledges made. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Willard S. Richardson, Charles O. Heydt, Herbert L. Hill, E. L. Ballard.
- Interdenominational Cooperative Movement
  - Interdenominational Cooperative Movement - The Christian Church, 1917-1918 (Box 38, Folder 314)
    Letters expressing interest in John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s address at Baptist Social Union dinner, and "Saturday Evening Post" article on "The Christian Church;" John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s letters of appreciation. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Willard S. Richardson, Ivy Lee, G. H. Lorimer, Oscar S. Strauss.
    46
  - Interdenominational Cooperative Movement - Christian Church Unity Address, 1917 - General, 1917-1921 (Box 38, Folder 315)
    Copy of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s article from "Saturday Evening Post," February 9, 1918. Correction of galley proof of article, reprinting article. Copy of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s paper "The Christian Church - What of Its Future?" Church Unity- Dr. W. A. Brown, E. D. Burton, W. P. Merrill, F. B. Smith, J. M. Speers, plans for Inter-Church Federation conference; advantages of church Federation. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s correspondence with Dr. Faunce and Dr. Woelfkin. Ad Interim Committee. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Charles O. Heydt, Robert W. Gumbel, Ivy Lee, J. M. Speers, C. Woelfkin, E. D. Burton, W. A. Brown, William P. Merrill, W. P. Faunce, J. D. Adam, Willard S. Richardson.
    46.1
  - Interdenominational Cooperative Movement - Christian Church Unity Address, 1917 - Newspaper Articles, 1917-1921 (Box 38, Folder 316)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s letters of appreciation for editorials about speech. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s address on future of the Church; letters of thanks for reprinting speech and for kindly sentiments. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Robert W. Gumbel, Ivy Lee.
  - Interdenominational Cooperative Movement - Interchurch World Movement, 1919-March 1920 (Box 38, Folder 317)